Get 'em!
!بيرش
Danny!
!دني
Atta boy!
!آفرين سر
Borrow money from me, you're expected to pay it back.
از من ول قرض رفتي ،حالا بايد برش ردوني
You pay it back, the collar stays on.
اين ردن بند يش من ميمونه تا ولمو بياري
You don't pay it back, the collar comes off.
اه نياريش ردن بند مال من ميشه
It's a simple set of rules.
يه قانون ساده هست
Give us your arm! Still! Shut up!
!دستتو بده!آخه!خفه شو
Behave! It's nice! We'll be back. Come on, Danny boy.
.مودب باش! قشنه! برمي رديم. يالا ،دني
I had a dream last night
ديشب يه خواب ديدم
I was sitting under those umbrellas
زير اون ترها نشسته بودم
that they make out of palm leaves, you know?
که با برهاي درخت خرما درست شده بودن،مي دونين؟
And these beautiful golden skinned girls dressed in...
...و اين دخترهاي وست طلايي خوشل
just, like, little grass skirts, the skin that they was born in.
با دامنهاي کوتاه علفي ، با وستي که باهاش به دنيا اومدن
And they came over, one after the other,
و يکي يکي اومدن جلو
and they brought me a drink in a coconut.
و توي يه ناريل برام شراب آوردن
And as they served me the drink, they brushed their tits across my face.
و همين جور که از من ذيرايي مي کردن ، سينه هاشون رو روي صورتم مي ماليدن
Cor, bloody hell...
خداي من ، بس کن
Hey, boss, I think Georgie's getting a chubby.
هي ، رئيس ، فکر کنم جورجي داره خل ميشه
You shut up, Lefty! You're the one getting a fucking hard on, not me!
خفه شو ، تويي که خودت رو اره مي کني تا سوار بشي ، نه من
Ah well,
خوب فتي
that was the end of the best bits.
اما اين ايان يزهاي خوش بود
After the girls, the whole thing turned to shit.
بعد از رفتن دختر ها همه يز به ند کشيده شد
This giant mumpet turned up with a machine gun and started blasting away
اين داي نره غول با تفنش ظاهر شد و آتش بازي رو شروع کرد
until there was nothing but blood and guts and bits of body everywhere.
و همه جا رو ر از خون و دل و روده و تکه هاي بدن کرد
Nice one!
ه آدم خوبي!
It was a real nightmare.
يه کابوس واقعي بود
I bet you've never had a dream in your life, have you?
شرط مي بندم تا حالا يه خواب هم تو عمرت نديده باشي، ديدي؟
Yeah, must be peaceful.
آره ، بايد آدم آرومي باشه
Here, have a bit of that. That's it, that's it...
...يک کمي از اونو اينجا دارم اينه، ايناهاش
I hate dreams.
از خواب متنفرم
Georgie boy!
!جورجي
Lefty
لفتي
Yo, Ricy, you mad bastard!
هي ، ريسي ، حرومزاده
Ricy, how did you get on?
ريسي ، طور سوار شدي ؟
Hello, Guv'nor. All my people paid to the penny.
سلام رئيس .افراد من به ني ول ميدن
Twenty seven hundred.
ميشه 2700 تا
Perfect! Give the lads a drink.
درسته!يه نوشيدني به اين سرا بده
Cheers, Guv'nor.
آفرين رئيس
What do you want done with Danny?
با دني کار ميکني؟
Well, sort him out. His face is bleeding. Sort him out.
خوب، بيرون مشغولش کن صورتش خونيه. ببرش بيرون
Anybody have any trouble?
کسي مشکلي داره؟
Put it on here.
بزارش اينجا
Oh nice, look at this!
اوه،اينو ببين
Come on Danny, you heard the guv'nor.
يالا دني، شنيدي رئيس ي فت
Here's a bonus. Alright?
اين جايزه توئه.طوره؟
Sort yourself out, OK?
برو بيرون خودتو مشغول کن
Come on Danny.
يالا دني
Danny!
!دني
Come on! Danny! Come on!
!يالا دني! يالا
Here, give us a pose!
اينجا، برامون يه ژست بير
Oh yeah, beautiful! Yeah...
...آره!خيلي قشنه!آره
Oi! Get back in the car.
اوي! بررد توي ماشين
Fuckin' beast!
حيوون لعنتي
Fucking wanker!
احمق لعنتي
I want to get closer.
ميخوام بياي نزديکتر
That's it.
حال خوبه
No, don't get your fingers on it. Your monkey.
نه انشتت رو بهش نزن. احمق
Give us it.
اونو بده من
Oh, hello!
!اوه،سلام
Look at him!
ناهش کن
No, not here!
نه ،اينجا نه
Yes, you're right. Let's go somewhere more comfortable.
آره ، راست ميي بريم يه جايي که راحت تر باشيم
You're so rough!
قدر زمختي
Yeah... Ruff! Ruff! Ruff!
!آره...روكي!روك!روك
No...
...نه
Turn the light on!
راغ رو روشن کن
No lights.
بدون راغ
Turn on the lights!
راغها رو روشن کن
I like to see you who I'm making love to.
ميخوام کسي رو دوست دارم ببينم
I don't.
نميخوام
What the fuck... Shit!
ندت بزنه
Fuck!
لعنتي
Jesus! You sick bastard!
يا مسيح! حرومزاده مريض
Oi! Oi! Where are you going?
کجا ميري؟
Much obliged!
ممنون
Fuckin'ell...
...لعنتي
Atta boy!
آفرين سر
No way, boss.
نميشه ، رئيس
Hey, Nigel!
هي، نيل
OK, Bart,
خيلي خوب ،بارت
All right... You want this?
باشه...اينو ميخواي؟
Turn it round, keep it running, and keep your eye out for the old bill.
دور بزن و ماشينو روشن بزار هار شمي مواظب باش
Good luck, son!
موفق باشي، سر
Luck? Don't need it, bruv!
موفقيت؟ لازمش ندارم
You know what I have always found fascinating
ميدوني رفيق من هميشه در مورد تموم کارهاي تو
about this whole situation of yours, Bart buddy?
ي رو فريبنده مي بينم؟
How you basically turned a man into a dog.
اصلاً طور يه مرد رو به س تبديل کردي؟
Well, it's like my sainted Mum used to say.
مادر مقدس ميه
Get 'em young enough and the possibilities are endless.
اونها رو به اندازه کافي جوون نه دار احتمالات بى ايان هستند
Unlike yours at the moment.
بر خلاف زمان تو
So let me work this through one more time.
س بزار يکبار ديه اون کارو بکنم
I don't pay you, you take his collar off.
من به تو ول يا حقوق نميدم تو ردن بندشو باز مي کني
Correctimundo.
درسته
You take his collar off, he beats us all to death,
تو ردن بندشو باز ميکني اونم ما رو به قصد کشت ميزنه
Now, who's the bright penny?
حالا، ني، باهوش کيه؟
So it's in my best interest to keep that collar on.
س خيلي دوست دارم که ردنبند بسته بمونه
Danny!
!دني
Kill him!
!بکشش
Danny! Kill him! Danny!
!دني! بکشش! دني
When you're finished with the master,
وقتي کارتون با صاحبش تموم شد
kill the dog.
س رو بکشين
You fuckin' bastard!
حرومزاده آشغال
Good to see you Mr. Yussef.
از ديدنتون خوشحالم آقاي يوسف
You fucker!
تو يه آشغالي
Kill!
!بکش
Find anything to you like yet?
يزي که دوست داشتي، يدا کردي؟
Not yet.
!هنوز نه
Stop him!!!
متوقفش کنيد
Nice puppy.
توله س خوبم
Atta boy!
سر
I don't know what it is with people...
...نميدونم راوقتي با مردم روبرو ميشم
Maybe I've got a speech deficiency.
شايد ديه نميتونم خوب حرف بزنم
Take what you want...
...هري مي خواي بردار
Oh, no. My mum didn't bring me up to be a pig.
نه.مامانم منو به دنيا نياورده که يه خوک کثيف باشم
Not like some people I know. I only take what I'm owed.
نه مثل بعضي ها که ميشناسمشون فقط هري که مال خودمه، بر ميدارم
But this time...
...اما اين دفعه
Yeah...
...آره
With a little interest.
با يک کمي سود
Because you are... Such a fucking Arsehole!!!
...آخه تو !!!يه  ---آشغالي
Asshole?
احمق
Come on.
يالا
What are you looking at?
به ي زل زدي؟
Just enjoying the show.
فقط از نمايش لذت مي برم
Good.
خوبه
Don't you ever leave my sight again!
ديه هيوقت نبايد شمتو از من برداري
You said "stay in the car".
فتي توي ماشين بمون
Shut the fuck up!
دهن شادتو ببند
Get in, you bitch!
!بيا تو! تويي هرزه
I don't believe it!
من قبولش ندارم
He just stood there and watched them beat the crap out of me!
فقط اونجا موند و تماشا کرد که مثل يه آشغال منو ميزدن
Even a dog has got the brains to come to his master's defense!
حتي يه س هم عقلش ميرسه که بياد از صاحبش دفاع کنه
Bite'em! Claw'em! Piss on 'em!
!اونها رو بيره!نشون بزنه!روشون بشاشه
Anything for fuck's sake! Jesus!
!هي غلطي نکرد!مسيح
Jesus, boss, you don't look too good.
يا مسيح، رئيس، انارحالت خوب نيست
Another original thinker.
يه متفکر اصيل ديه
No, I just meant that maybe you might want to go home.
نه، فقط منظورم اين بود که شايد بخواين برين خونه
What's next?
بعدي يه؟
Just the antiques place.
فقط جاي عتيقه ها مونده
No, let's do it.
نه، بريم انجامش بديم
Are you sure you're up to this?
مطمئني سرحالي؟
No, no, you let one of them payments slide
نه ،نه ، تو به يکي از اونها که حسابي ول بدي
and they'll all turn into original thinkers.
همه اونها به متفکرهاي واقعي تبديل ميشن
Find a decent pub first, though, I want a pint.
اول يه مشروب فروشي  يدا کن فکر کنم يه يک لازم دارم
And you, you useless piece of shit!
و تو، يه آشغال بي مصرفي
Right... Now... Here's the plan.
...درسته...حالا...يه نقشه داريم
I'm going to try and settle this in a peaceful and professional manner.
ميخوا م در کمال حرفه اي ري و آرامش يه تسويه حساب بکنم
But if that doesn't work, I'm gonna press this...
...ولي اه کارها درست يش نرفت بايد اينو فشارش بدم
Oi! Oi!!
!!اوي! اوي
You pay attention!
!خوب وش کن
When I press this button, this red light is gonna start blinking. Right?
وقتي اين دمه رو فشار ميدم اين راغ قرمز شمک ميزنه. درسته؟
The red light blinks, you go through that door
راغ قرمز شمک ميزنه و تو ميري توي اون در
quicker than a mouse chasing a bit of cheese.
سريعتر از موشي که دنبال يه تيکه نيره
Keep your hands off him, will you? And stop fucking smirking!
دست که بهش نميزني، ميزني؟ و اين وزخند مسخره رو هم تمومش کن
The red light blinks... Look at me!
!راغ قرمز شمک ميزنه...منو ناه کن
Concentrate! The red light blinks, you go through the door.
تمرکز کن! راغ قرمز که شمک بزنه از اون در ميري تو
That's all you gotta remember. Right?
همه اينها بايد يادت بمونه. باشه؟
Light. Door
راغ. در
Oi! Right... And don't take your eyes off the light. And don't let me down.
اوي! درسته...شمهاتو از راغ برنميداري و مأيوسم نميکني
Georgie!
!جورجي
Yes, Bart.
بله
Hang that up there.
اونو اونجا آويزون کن
Up there?
اون بالا؟
All right.
آره
The light, Danny, the light.
.راغ، دني، راغ
Red means go. Right?
قرمز يعني برو. باشه؟
Ay ay ay ay ay!
آي ياي ياي ياي ياي!
Sounds like someone in here could use my help!
صداها نشون ميدن يه کسي اينجاست که ميتونه کمکم کنه
Hi, how you doing?
طور اينکارو ميکني؟
I'm just gonna tune these pianos.
فقط اين يانوها رو کوک ميکنم
Probably be a couple of hours.
ميتونم دوساعتي اينجا باشم
If you don't mind.
ار ايرادى نداره
You like pianos?
يانو رو دوست داري؟
Yeah, me too.
آره، منم دوست دارم
This whole place is like... it's like a big treasure chest.
اين مکان دست نخورده مثل يه صندوق نج بزره
Probably gonna be a whole month getting all these ladies back into health.
شايد يه ماه کامله که همه اين خانومها رو سرحال مياره
You know tuning pianos is really hard work
ميدوني کوک کردن يانو واقعاً کار سختيه
and my back isn't what it used to be.
و منم ديه نميتونم مثل ذشته اين کارو بکنم
Are you... Are you doing anything important right now?
تو طور...الان داري کار مهمي ميکني؟
Cause I could really use a hand here. How about it?
اي کاش يه دست ديه ميتونيت کمکم کنه.نظرت يه؟
Please.
خواهش ميکنم
Are you still there?
هنوز اونجايي؟
You are, aren't you?
تويي، تو نيستي؟
Yes.
آره
Good, good,
خوبه ، خوبه
come on!
بجنب
You know a lot of people think because a piano's so big, it is very strong
ميدوني خيلي از مردم فکر ميکنن ون يانو خيلي نده هست، خيلي قويه
and you can just pound it any way you want to and nothing will happen,
و تو ميتوني هرجوري بخواي بکوبيش و هي اتفاقي نيفته
but that's not so at all.
اما اصلاً اينجوري نيست
Pianos are a lot like people. I mean, you pound on a person,
يانو ها خيلي شبيه مردم هستن منظورم اينه که وقتي روي يه نفر ميکوبي
they get out of tune. Same with a piano. You pound on 'em and...
ازکوک خارج ميشه.مثل يانو اونها رو ميکوبي
Lordy, listen to that. Sad as a baby crying.
لوردي،وش کن.غمناک مثل ريه به
I tell you what I want you to do now.
الان ميم  برام کار کني
When I say press, I want you to press on this key.
وقتي ميم بزن،مي خوام روي اين کليد بزني
Starting with this one right here and going to the right.
از اين کليد شروع ميشه و بسمت راست ميره
One, then two, then three.
يک ،بعد 2،بعد 3
Think you can do that?
فکر ميکني بتوني؟
OK. Put your hand here, just like that.
باشه.دستتو بزار اينجا،درست مثل اون
Right there.
درست همينجا
Oh oh my goodness.
عاليه
Oh wait a minute. Loosen up. Loosen up.
اوه يه لحظه صبر کن
Music's got to flow from within, y'know.
موسيقي بايد از درونت بياد بيرون،ميفهمي
Can't flow if you're all stiff.
اه سيخ بموني نميتونه بياد بيرون
On the key there. Just relax.
روي اون کليد،خونسرد باش
Nothing to be afraid of.
يزي نيست که بترسي
There we are. Are you ready?
خوب حالا حاضري؟
And press.
و بزن
Little harder.
يک کم محکمتر
Good! Again.
خوبه!دوباره
Good. Listen,
خوبه.وش کن
you show a real talent for this sort of work.
استعداد خيلي خوبي براي اينکار داري
OK,
باشه
press it again.
دوباره بزن
Press.
بزن
Oh wonderful.
اوه شفت آوره
And one more time.
و يه بار ديه
Ready?
حاضري؟
Press, press,
بزن،بزن
go ahead relax.
راحت باش
Let the energy flow.
بزار انرژي بياد بيرون
Let the magic happen.
بزار جادو بشه
Good, good, good, good...
...خوبه،خوبه،خوبه،خوبه
Excellent, excellent!
فوق العاده است
Wait, wait! Hold on! Now...
...صبرکن،صبر کن!نهش دار!حالا
You want to see what you did?
ميخواي ببيني کار کردي؟
Yes.
بله
Check this out.
اينو ببين
That the sweetest sound or what?
اون مطبوعترين صدايه يا يز ديه؟
Yes.
بله
Want to try it?
مي خواي دوباره امتحانش کني؟
Here, c'mon. Put your hand here.
اينجا ،يالا،دستتو بزار اينجا
Put your fingers right there. There. Right there.
انشتهاتو درست اونجا بزار اونجا،درست اونجا
Hit it.
بزنش
Next stop Carnegie Hall.
توقف بعدي تالار کارني
You know about Carnegie hall?
در باره تالار کارني يزي شنيدي؟
It's this big place in New York City.
همين جاي بزر،توي نيويورکه
All the great musicians want to play Carnegie Hall.
همه موسيقي دانهاي بزر دلشون ميخواد توي تالار کارني اجرا داشته باشن
I did too.
منم همينطور
When I was growing up, it was my big ambition.
از کوکي آرزوي بزر من بود
But I never was that good a musician.
اما هيوقت نشد يه موسيقي دان خوب بشم
Are you OK?
روبه راهي؟
Yes
آره
Good.
خوبم
What's your name?
اسمت يه؟
OK. Alright, alright.
خيلي خوب. باشه
Mister No Name.
استاد بي نام
My name is Sam.
اسمم سم هست
Pleased to meet you.
از ديدارتون خوشحال شدم
Me too.
منم همينطور
Good, that's good.
خوبه،اون خوبه
So tell me something, Mr. No Name,
س يه يزي به من بو،آقاي بي اسم
am I hearing a sort of clicking sound?
ببينم ، من دارم يه صداي تق تق مي شنوم؟
Do you hear it? Or is it...
...مي شنويش؟يا اينکه اون
I'm gonna sell you, is what I'm gonna do!
ميخوام بفروشمت. آره حتماً اينکارو ميکنم
If you can't do what I've trained you to do, what fucking use are you?
اه نميتوني يزي رو که به تو ياد دادم انجام بدي،س به ه دردي ميخوري؟
No fucking use is the answer! No fucking use at all!
!جواب اينه که به هي دردي !اصلاً به هي دردي
I feed you! I clothe you! I put a roof over your head!
!من به تو غذا دادم!لباس دادم!يه سرناه دادم
And all that time I put in. All the fucking effort!
!توي تموم اين مدت باهات کنار اومدم!توي هر کار مزخرفي
To make you the man that you are...
...از تو مردي رو ساختم که هستي
And what gratitude do I get! Look at me!
!ه تشکري عايدم شد!به من ناه کن
I look as if I've just been through the third fucking world war.
انار که فقط من توي  اون جن جهاني سوم مزخرف بودم
Take him downstairs, get him out of my sight.
ببرش ايين،از جلوي شمهام دورش کن
C'mon, c'mon.
زودتر، بجنب
I'm getting too old for this shit.
بخاطر اين آشغاله که دارم خيلي ير ميشم
All right, Danny. Get in! Get in!
!خيلي خوب، دني. برو تو! برو تو
I'm busy!
سرم شلوغه
I said get in there.
فتم  برو اون تو
There's a man here to see you.
يه مرده اينجاست که ميخواد تو رو ببينه
I just told you I'm busy!
بهت فتم که سرم شلوغه
He says he's got a business proposition for us.
ميه برامون يه بيزينس  يشنهاد داره
He says it's about the show you put on today.
ميه درمورد نمايشي هست که امروز انجام دادي
Pat him down.
بيارش ايين
Already did.
تاحالا اومده
All right, wheel him in.
باشه، بفرستش تو
Receiving fucking visitors looking like this. It's a joke.
الان ه وقت اين ملاقات کننده هاي لعنتيه خنده داره
Shit, Jesus! Fuckin'ell!
!ندت بزنه،يا عيسي مسيح!ه آشغالي
I'm listening.
دارم وش ميدم
That was a very impressive display
نمايش خيلي خوبي بود
your man put on in the jewelry shop today.
امروز توي جواهر فروشى
I assure you, it was entirely justified.
بهتون اطمينان ميدم اون کاملاً توجيه شده بود
I'm sure it was.
مطمئنم که بود
That thing with the collar. Brilliant.
اون يز با ردن بند. زيرکانه است
And the point of this conversation is?
و هدف اين فتو؟
The point of this conversation is, I'd like to offer you a lucrative proposition.
هدف از اين فتو اينه که دوست داشتم يشنهاد يه کار رسود رو به تو بدم
How lucrative?
قدر رسود؟
Very lucrative. Should I continue?
خيلي رسوده.ادامه بدم؟
Please...
...خواهش ميکنم
It's an entertainment I produce for some friends once a month.
يه سررميه که ماهي يه باربراي بعضي از رفقا روبه راه  مي کنم
Members only, so to speak.
فقط اعضا،
What?
ي؟
And we're always on the lookout for new talent.
و ما هميشه از دور دنبال استعدادهاي جديد ميرديم
The first fight is a tryout. For that, you get fifteen thousand.
اولين جن آزمايش استعداد يابيه بخاطرش 15هزار تا يرت مياد
For the second twenty, plus the right to bet.
بيست تاي بعدي به حق شرط بندي اضافه ميشه
We had one chap
ما يه جوانک داشتيم
who after fees and betting on himself got up to half a million a fight.
کسيکه روي خودش شرط ببنده و ول بزاره نيم ميليون از ول يه مبارزه رو مييره
That's only if you win, of course.
البته درصورتيکه برنده بشي
But how do you get to win?
اما طور ميخواي ببري؟
It's to the death.
آخرش مره
So glad you could make it.
خوشحال باش که تونستي کارشو بسازي
Please follow me.
دنبالم بيا
Where's the money?
ول کجاست؟
Oh well, the money comes after.
اوه  خوبه،ول بعداً ميرسه
After what?
کي؟
After you beat him, our current champion.
بعداز اينکه قهرمان فعلي مارو زدي
Undefeated in fifteen bouts.
الان 15 دور هست که شکست نخورده
Care for a glass of champagne?
براي يه بطري شاماين نراني؟
We won't be here that long.
زياد اينجا نمي مونيم
Kill him.
بکشش
Rip his fucking hat off!
اون کلاه مسخره اش رو بردار
That's my boy!
اون سرمه
Thanks for the opportunity. You're most welcome. Very impressive.
ممنون که افتخار دادين.خيلي خوش آمدين.خيلي جالبه
That bit with the collar. How did you do that?
اون سر با ردن بند. طور اينکارو کردي؟
Like my saint of a mum used to say:
فکر کنم مادر مقدس ميه
Get 'em young and the possibilities are endless.
ار جوان باشي ، امکانات نامحدودي داري
I thought it was the Jesuits who said that.
فکر کنم اين جمله مال انجمن عيسي باشه
Probably got it from my mum.
شايد از مادرم شنيده باشم
If you want us back you do know where to find me.
اه ميخواي ما رو برردوني ميدوني که کجا دنبالمون بياي
Oh we certainly want you back.
اوه ما حتماً ميخواهيم برردي
Only, if you could make it a little more ... entertaining... next time.
فقط اه تونستي اين دفعه يک کمي بيشتر...سررم کننده اش کن
I'll see what I can do.
ببينم ه کاري ميتونم بکنم
Here, remember I told you about that dream I had?
اينجا،يادته به تو فتم ه خوابي ديده بودم؟
What? The one with the all the birds in it?
ي؟يه خواب با کلي رنده توش؟
Yeah.
آره
Well, I figured it all out. D'you know who Freud is?
خوب،همه اش رو تجسم کردم ميدوني فرويد کيه؟
No.
نه
Well that doesn't matter. Freud was a genius
خوب مهم نيست، فرويد يه نابغه بود
and his whole thing was if you dream something
و همه يزش اين بود که اه خواب يزي رو ببيني
it means something else.
هريز ديري که باشه
Like the girls, the island, the drink. They were just symbols.
مثل دخترها، جزيره، شراب اونها فقط نماد بودن
What they actually represented was like comfort, relaxation,
يزي که اونها به آدم ميدادن راحتي و آرامش بود
no worries.
نه دل نراني
And then this swell turns up offering us
اونوقت اين خوشي براي عرضه به ما ظاهر ميشه
more money than we could save in 20 years.
بيشتر از ولي بود که ظرف 20 سال ميتونستيم جمع کنيم
Well, it all becomes clear.
خوب،همه اش ازبين رفت
The dream. The swell. It means retirement, you get it?
رويا.خوشي .معنيش بازنشستيه،رفتيش؟
Yeah, right.
آره ، درسته
No more filthy collections, no more beatings.
بدون جمع کردن ولهاي کثيف ، فارغ از زد و خوردها
I tell you, I feel really good here.
ميم،من اينجا احساس خيلي خوبي دارم
I feel generous.
احساس بخشندي ميکنم
Danny, what do you want?
دني،تو ي ميخواي؟
A piano.
يه يانو
Excuse me?
ببخشيد؟
I want a piano.
يه يانو ميخوام
A piano. Yeah, leave off. How about a lobster dinner?
يه يانو.آره،دست بردار با يه شام خرن دريايي طوري؟
I want a piano.
من يه يانو ميخوام
How about a woman? You've never had a woman.
زن طور؟ تو تاحالا زن نداشتي
Danny, you're starting to piss me off.
دني، باز داري مي شاشي رو اعصابم
That's what I love about you, Danny.
هموني هست که درمورد تو عاشقشم،دني
One thought at a time.
همزمان توي يه فکر
That's what makes us such a good team.
اين همونيه که ما رو يه تيم خوب ميکنه
The brains and the brawn.
مغزها و عضله
I tell you this is gonna be one lovely day!
ميم امروز بايد يه روز دوست داشتني باشه
Let's go.
بيا بريم
Good morning Ladies,
صبح بخير خانومها
how are we all this morning?
امروز صبح حالمون طوره؟
Ah, here you are.
آه،بفرماييد
You've been very patient, waiting for me, Madam.
خانم ،شما خيلي صبوريد که منتظر من موندين
So I'm going to devote myself to you all day.
بنابراين ميخوام همه روزمو به شما اختصاص بدم
Who's there? It's you, isn't it?
کي اونجاست؟تويي،نيستي؟
Yes.
آره
Well, isn't that something?
خوب،اون يزيه؟
You know, I went right home and I told Victoria, my step-daughter...
...ميدوني،من رفتم خونه و به ويکتوريا فتم، نادختري من
I told Victoria all about you.
درباره تو با ويکتوريا حرف زدم
Hello?
ســـلام؟
Don't tell me you're still asleep.
بهم نو که هنوز خوابي
Well now...
...حالا خوبه
If I was a fella who woke up in a strange house
اه منم کسي بودم که توي خونه غريبه بيدار شده
wearing someone else's pajamas, I would be pretty nervous.
و لباس خواب يکي ديه تنم باشه بايدم اينجور عصباني بشم
I'd try to find the safest place I could to hide.
سعي مي کردم يه جاي امن يدا کنم بتونم توش مخفي بشم
Now, when I was a kid, the safest place in the whole wide world was...
...وقتي به بودم امنترين جاي تموم دنيا
Right where you are.
درست جايي بود که تو هستي
It does feel safe, doesn't it?
بنظر امن مياد،نه؟
Well, I figured a man who'd been out for two days would wake up pretty hungry.
خوب،من مردي رو تصور کردم که 2 روز بيرون بوده وبايد رسنه از خواب اشه
So, I hope you like peanut butter and jelly.
س،اميدوارم از کره بادام زميني و ژله خوشت بياد
My name is Sam, remember?
اسمم سمه،يادته؟
OK you take your time.
باشه. تو وقت داري
Victoria and I are not big on asking questions.
من و ويکتوريا توي سوال کردن وارد نيستيم
Figure when the person is ready, they'll give their answers. OK?
حواست هم باشه که ه وقتي مردم آماده هستن، جواب بدن. باشه؟
OK.
باشه
Hi!
سلام
He's cute!
!اون جذابه
Really?
واقعاً؟
I like his haircut it's like when I was six and used to cut my own hair.
از مدل موهاش خوشم مياد مثل وقتيه که 6 سالم بود و موهامو اونجوري ميذاشتم
Yeah, well...
...آره،خوبه
You and Mom thought it was cute.
تو و مامان خيال مي کردين که اون جذابه
He's not six.
اون 6 سالش نيست
More is than not, I bet.
بيشتر هست تا اينکه نباشه شرط مي بندم
Does he like to read?
از خوندن خوشش مياد؟
Well I don't know.
خوب،نميدونم
Does he like to write? Does he like to draw?
از نوشتن خوشش مياد؟ از نقاشي خوشش مياد؟
Sweetie, I don't know anything about him.
عزيزم،من هيي درباره اون نميدونم
Well, that's not altogether so. He likes music.
.خوب، اونقدرهم نمي شناسمش از موسيقي خوشش مياد
Cool.
خوبه
Hi!
سلام
Sam said you like music.
سم فت که از موسيقي خوشت مياد
You know how to use it?
بلدي باهاش کار کني؟
See...
...ببين
Nice, huh?
خوبه؟
It was my Dad's.
مال درمه
He died before I was born and then my mom gave it to me.
اون قبل از اينکه بدنيا بيام مرد و مادرم اونو به من داد
But she died in a car accident. But not until after she married Sam.
اما اونم توي تصادف ماشين مرد ولي
He was my dad's best friend.
اون بهترين دوست درم بود
Am I talking too much? You know because I do that some times.
زياد حرف ميزنم؟ميدوني بخاطر اينکه بعضي وقتها اون کارو ميکنم
And if you're bored listening and I just keep going on and on,
و اه از وش دادن خسته ميشي و من همينطور دارم ادامه ميدم
you just tell me, OK?
کافيه به من بي،باشه؟
I'm gonna go help Sam with dinner.
من دارم ميرم توي ختن شام،به سم کمک کنم
You can join us if you'd like. Or you can eat under here.
اه دوست داشتي ميتوني بياي يش ما يااينکه ميتوني همين ايين بخوري
It's just the food goes down easier if you eat it sitting up.
اه راست بشيني،غذا هم راحتتر ايين ميره
You don't burp so much.
زياد آروغ نزن
My name's Victoria.
اسمم هست ويکتوريا
Should I go get him?
بايد برم بيرمش؟
No, let's let him get himself.
نه،بزار خودش بيره
Maybe he doesn't know how.
شايد بلد نباشه
Well, then let's just give him the opportunity to learn.
خوب، اونوقت اين شانسو بهش ميديم که ياد بيره
There's nothing like self-discovery for turning a boy into a man.
هيي مثل خودشناسي نميتونه يه سر رو به يه مرد تبديل کنه
How do you know? You never had a boy.
از کجا ميدوني؟ تو تاحالا سر نداشتي
I was speaking from self experience, if you don't mind.
داشتم از روي تجربه خودم حرف ميزدم البته ار ايرادى نداره
I was a boy myself once, you know.
ميدوني، زماني خودم يه سربودم
No way.
واقعاً
Yes, way. Come on.
آره ، يالا
Thank you for the food we are about to eat.
براي غذا ممنونيم ما داريم غذا ميخوريم
Thank you for peace this house possesses.
بخاطر صلح و صفاي اين خونه ممنونيم
Thank you for another day of health and happiness.
براي يه روز خوب و شاد ديه ازت ممنونيم
And please make sure Victoria kicks butt on her piano recital.
و خواهش مي کنم کاري کن که ويکتوريا در تکنوازي يانو موفق بشه
I thought we're not supposed to ask for things.
فکر مي کردم نبايد اين يزها رو درخواست کنيم
Says who?
از کي حرف ميزني؟
Says you. Since I was a little girl you told me those are the rules.
تو رو ميم. از وقتيکه يه دختربه بودم به من فتي که اونها قانون هستن
You mean I didn't tell you about
يعني ميخواي بي به تو نفتم
the special exemption for very Important Piano Recitals?
که تکنوازيهاي خيلي مهم يانو از اين قضيه مستثني هستن؟
Oh yeah right. Exemptions. I buy that... Not.
آره درسته. استثناء. من خريدمش...نه
You know I liked it better when you just agreed with everything I said.
ميدوني وقتي با هريزي که فتم موافقت کردي فکر کردم اون بهتره
How about some soup?
با يکمي سو طوري؟
Well, you're just in time.
خوبه، درست به موقع
This is your place.
اين جاي توئه
Come on, sit down.
يالا،بشين
Victoria would you...
...ويکتوريا ميشه
Sure. Sam made this. It's his world famous potato and leek soup.
مطمئن باش. سم درستش کرده سو سيب زميني و تره فرني اون تو دنيا معروفه
World famous.
تو دنيا معروفه
There's your napkin.
اين دستمال توئه
Bread?
نون؟
Oh no! This is a spoon. And this... ... is your spoon. Like this...
...اوه نه! اين يه قاشقه. و اين ...قاشق توئه. مثل اين...
Oh my...
...اوه
Oh, great! A duet.
اوه ،عاليه!يه همخواني دونفري
My name is Danny.
اسمم دنيه
I think we won't put a bandage back on and we'll let some air get to this.
فکر کنم بهتره شت زخم رو نبنديم و بزاريم يکمي هوا بهش برسه
You're gonna be just fine.
خوب ميشي
I've been meaning to ask you.
ميخواستم يه يزي از تو برسم
What is this?
اين يه؟
OK. No problem.
باشه.اشکال نداره
I wasn't going to take it off.
نميخواستم اونو بردارم
Y'know, when I was a kid I had a cowboy hat.
ميدوني،وقتي به بودم يه کلاه کابويي داشتم
I slept in it, I ate in it, I bathed in it.
روش ميخوابيدم،توش غذا ميخوردم،باهاش آبتني ميکردم
Anybody tried to take it off, I had the same reaction.
هرکسي ميخواست اونو برداره همين عکس العمل رو نشون ميدادم
So...
...س
Anyway, I've been thinking. You been cooped up in here for weeks now.
بهرحال، فکر کنم الان هفته هاست که خودتو اينجا زندوني کردي
Would you like to get some fresh air?
نبايد از يک کم هواي تازه بدت بياد؟
Stretch your legs?
اهاتو دراز کني؟
It's nice outside.
بيرون خوبه
It's nice in here.
اينجا هم خوبه
You're afraid that if you go out you won't be able to come back in?
ميترسي اه بري بيرون ديه نتوني برردي تو؟
We'll come back. Promise.
برميرديم. قول ميدم
Alright, we'll be back to get you at 3 o'clock.
باشه، من ساعت 3 ميام دنبالت
I am 18, Sam.
من 18 سالمه، سم
Yeah, for a whole week and a half.
آره، يه هفته و نيم کامل
Don't worry.
نران نباش
3 o'clock.
ساعت 3
Bye
باي
You all right?
حق با شماهاست؟
She kissed me.
اون منو بوسيد
Yeah, I know, she does that. How was it?
.آره،ميدونم،اون کارو کرد اون طور بود؟
Wet.
نمناک
Is that all?
همه اش همين؟
Nice.
خوب
Wet. Nice.
.نمناک.خوب
Sounds like what a kiss ought to feel like.
از صداي يه بوس ميشه احساسشو فهميد
Come on, we've got a lot to do.
يالا،کارهاي زيادي بايد انجام بديم
- Hello, luv. Love. - Good morning Maddy.
سلام،لو. صبح بخير مدي
Maddy runs the best supermarket in all of Glasgow.
مدي بهترين سورمارکت رو توي الاسکو داره
Maddy, this is Danny.
مدي،اين دنيه
Hello, Danny.
سلام،دني
- He's a little shy. - I like my men to be shy.
يک کم کمروئه من دوست دارم که مشتريهام کمرو باشن
Presents a challenge for a girl.
به يه دختر جرات سريي ميده
I'm just going give him some of the finer points of shopping.
من فقط مي خوام بعضي از فوت و فن هاي خريد رو به اون ياد بدم
Couldn't have a better teacher.
معلم بهتري نميتونست داشته باشه
My mother could take two stones and a cup of water
مادرم ميتونست با دو تا سن ميوه و يه فنجان آب
and make a three course meal.
سه جور غذا درست کنه
As soon as I was old enough, she gave me the secret to great cooking.
وقتيکه به قدر کافي بزر شدم راز اون ختن عالي رو به من ياد داد
And now I'm going to teach it to you.
و الان ميخوام که اونو به تو ياد بدم
So, you ready to learn the secret to great cooking?
س،آ ماده شو تا راز اون ختن عالي رو ياد بيري
Yes.
باشه
OK, here it is.
خوب ،اون راز در اينه
Food talks.
غذا حرف ميزنه
Food talks?
غذا حرف ميزنه؟
Didn't know that, did you?
نميدونستي ،نه؟
No
نه
Food talks.
غذا حرف ميزنه
It will tell you everything you need to know.
اون هريزي رو که لازمه به تو ميه
All you have to do is learn the language.
کافيه که زبانشو ياد بيري
Take this melon here for instance, now.
مثلاً اين خربزه رو در نظر بير
What do you think that's saying?
فکر ميکني ي ميه؟
Yeah, but it's also saying "I am ripe".
"آره،اما اون داره ميه "من رسيده ام
You know what ripe means, don't you?
ميدوني رسيده يعني ي، نميدوني؟
No.
نه
Ripe means sweet. And sweet means good.
رسيده يعني شيرين و شيرين يعني اينکه خوبه
The kiss was ripe.
اون بوس هم رسيده بود
No, no. The kiss was sweet.
نه، نه. بوس شيرين نبود
The melon is ripe.
خربزه رسيده است
But ripe means sweet.
ولي رسيده يعني شيرين
Well, when you're talking about food.
خوبه، وقتي داري درباره غذا حرف ميزني
Kisses are nourishing in their own way but kisses are...
...بوسه ها هم براي خودشون خوشمزه هستن
Kisses are complicated. For now, let's just stick to melons.
ولي ييده اند فعلاً به اين خربزه برسيم، باشه؟
You go ahead, you try it.
تو يشرفت کردي، دوباره سعي کن
And don't forget, use the language.
و فراموش نکن که از زبونت استفاده کني
Oh, okay. How was that sound?
اوه، خب، اون صدا طور بود؟
It's ripe.
رسيده و جا افتاده بود
OK, ripe means?
خب، رسيده يعني ي؟
Ripe is sweet.
رسيده يعني شيرين
And sweet means?
و شيرين يعني ي؟
Sweet means good.
شيرين يعني خوب
Alright! My man! Put it up there!
بسيار خوب مرد من! اون رو بذار اون بالا
Thank you.
ممنونم
This is the cone and this is the ice cream.
اين قيفه و اين هم بستني
You ever have ice cream before?
تاحالا بستني رفتي؟
No.
نه
Well, this is vanilla ice cream. Vanilla's white.
.خوب، اين بستني وانيليه.وانيلي سفيده
Vanilla is white.
وانيلي سفيده
Go on, taste it.
خيلي خوب،امتحانش کن
Oh no, just work it around. Work it around.
اوه نه،بردونش فقط اين ور و اون ورش کن
Oh my god!
!خداي من
You know the thing about ice cream is first it's cold, but then it's sweet
يزيکه درباره بستني بايد بدوني اينه که اولش سرده،ولي بعد خوشمزه ميشه
and if you freeze your mouth out,
و اه دهنت يخ بزنه
you're never gonna be able to taste the sweet part.
هيوقت نميتوني قسمت شيرينشو بشي
So look here's how you do it...
...س ناه کن که طور اونو بخوري
Sweet is good.
شيريني خوبه
Yeah right. So look. You lick...
آره درسته.خوب ناه کن.ليس بزن
Like that...
...اينجوري
There you go.
انجام بده
How's that?
طوره؟
Look, you're getting it everywhere!
ببين، داري همه رو ميريزي اينور اونور
Shit, actually, we should really hurry.
لعنتي، واقعاً، بايد خيلي عجله کنيم
Come on.
بجنب
You OK?
رو براهي؟
Yeah.
آره
Finish it quickly.
زودتر تمومش کن
Remember, if Sam asks where we were, you let me do the talking.
يادت باشه، اه سم رسيد کجا بودين بزار من حرف بزنم
If he knows we had ice cream before dinner,
اه  اون بدونه که قبل از شام بستني خورديم
he'll be pissed we ruined our appetite. Understand?
ميشاشه به اشتهامون، فهميدي؟
What's "appetite"?
اشتها" ديه يه؟"
Appetite's what you have if you don't have a belly full of ice cream.
اه يه شکم ر از بستني نخورده باشي اشتها همون يزيه که به تو دست ميده
How's my mouth?
دهنم طوره؟
Nice.
خوبه
No it's not. It's full of hardware. But not for much longer.
نه نيست. ر از آشغاله. ديه نيست
Do you miss your mom?
مادرت رو از دست ميدي؟
Everyday. You miss your mom?
هر روز. مادرت رو از دست ميدي؟
I don't remember my mom.
مادرمو يادم نمياد
Sometimes I think it'd be easier not to remember.
بعضي وقتها فکر ميکنم بهتره که يادم نياد
Hi
سلام
You're late...
...دير رسيدين
It was so nice out we decided to walk the long way.
بيرون خيلي خوب بود ما هم تصميم رفتيم بيشتر راه بريم
Oh you deci...
...اوه تو تصمميم
Didn't I say bring her straight home?
نفتم يه راست بيارش خونه؟
Sam, it was me. Not him.
سم،اين من بودم.نه اون
Oh, it was...
...اوه ،اون بود
If you wanted to take the long way home,
اه ميخواستي تا خونه اينقدر راه بياي
Victoria, you could have gone to that school in Kansas.
ويکتوريا،تاحالا به اون مدرسه توي کانزاس رسيده بودي
Then you could have taken the long way home for fifty miles and I wouldn't care.
س تو 50 مايل تا خونه راه اومدي و من نران نباشم
Fifty miles of corn.
از کورن 50 مايل
Corn is safe.
کورن امنه
Corn is boring. And anyway this was the better school.
کورن کسل کننده است.بهرحال اين مدرسه بهتر بود
Which is why we're here and not with the corn, right?
ما بهمين خاطر اينجاييم و با کورن نيستيم،درسته؟
So do me a favor, huh, don't make me worry.
.س يه لطفي برام بکن،باشه،ديه نرانم نکن
OK, Sam.
باشه،سم
What is that?
اون يه؟
What?
ي؟
Smells like ice cream. Vanilla ice cream.
بوي بستني ميده. بستني وانيلي
Vanilla is white.
وانيل سفيده
First it's cold.
اولش سرده
Then it's sweet.
بعد شيرين ميشه
Sweet is good.
شيريني خوبه
Victoria?
ويکتوريا؟
Yeah?
بله؟
Sometimes, I worry about that boy.
بعضى اوقات،نران اون سر ميشم
It's as if something or someone has made him
انار که کسي يا يزي اونو ساخته باشه
shut down his feelings so hard, he can no longer get in touch with them.
احساساتشو شديداً خفه کردن بيشتر از اين نميتونه با اونها درتماس باشه
That's what I've been trying to get him to do.
براي همينه که من سعي ميکنم سرشو رم کنم
With vanilla ice cream?
با بستني وانيلي؟
Maybe we should come up with some different strategies.
احتمالاً ما بايد از يه راه ديه استفاده کنيم
Goodnight.
شب بخير
C 'mon, but shhhh...
...يالا،اما اووووو
When I was little I used to do this with my mom and Sam.
وقتي کويک بودم با مادرم و سم از اين استفاده ميکرديم
It's kinda how I fell in love with music.
اون کيندا هست قدر احساس ميکنم عاشق موزيکم
See these thingies?
اين يزها رو مي بيني؟
They're called notes.
بهشون مين نت
Notes.
نت
OK. Notes are signals.
آره.نت ها علائم قراردادي هستن
Notes are signals.
نت هاعلائم قراردادي هستن
OK.
باشه
So if you see this note,
اه اين نت رو ببيني
it's the signal to play this key.
اين علامت خش اين کليده
And this one,
و اين يکي
this key.
اين کليد
And this one, this key.
و اين يکي،اين کليد
Right. So you're gonna play and you're gonna hop...
...درسته. واقعاً داري اجرا ميکني و وول ميخوري
Great!
!عاليه
Ready?
آماده اي؟
I'm gonna go.
دارم ميرم
Keep going don't stop.
همينطور ادامه بده متوقفش نکن
Not ripe.
نرسيده
Hello, Sam.
سلام ،سم
Hi, Maddy.
سلام،مدي
How's the lessons going?
درسها طور يش ميره؟
Oh, he's growing by leaps and bounds. What is this you got here? Is this...?
اوه، اون خيلي سريع درحال يشرفته اين يه آوردي اينجا؟ اون...؟
Too ripe.
خيلي رسيده هست
Hey, get back here!
!برردونش اينجا
Get back here! C'mere! C'mere! C'mere!
!برردونش اينجا! بيااينجا! بيااينجا! بيااينجا
Alex, go the other side quick!
الکس،زود برو اونطرف
Get back here, you bastard!
بررد اينجا،حرامزاده
Alex, other side!
!الکس،اونطرف
Where's Danny? Danny!
!دني کجاست؟دني
That's ripe!
اون خته هست
Danny!
!دني
This one's ripe.
اين يکي رسيد هست
Danny, do you remember
دني، يادته
when I said that Victoria and I were not big on asking questions,
وقتي که فتم من و ويکتوريا توي سئوال کردن وارد نيستيم
that we thought when people were ready they'd give their own answers?
و توي اين فکر بوديم که مردم ه وقتي آماده بودن که جواب بدن؟
I remember.
يادمه
After today in the supermarket,
امروز توي سورمارکت
I need some answers,
يه سري جواب لازم دارم
and I don't think I'm going to get them without asking the questions.
و فکر نکنم بخوام بدون سئوال کردن بيرمشون
Is that alright?
درسته؟
OK.
آره
Ok, so... In the market those men, they were fighting.
خوب...توي فروشاه اون مردها داشتن دعوا ميکردن
You knew that, right?
اونو ميدونستي، درسته؟
Yes.
آره
But that didn't bother you?
ولي اين تو رو ناراحت نکرد؟
No.
نه
You weren't afraid?
نمي ترسيدي؟
Normally people find themselves in situations like that, they get afraid.
معمولاً کسايي که توي اين وضعيت باشن ميترسن
They weren't fighting me.
اونها با من دعوا نداشتن
OK. One more question.
باشه.يه سوال ديه
When you first came to us, you were hurt pretty bad.
اول که يش ما اومدي زخم و زيلي بودي
How did that happen?
طور اتفاق افتاد؟
I asked for a piano.
من يه يانو خواستم
You asked who for a piano?
از ه کسي يه يانو خواستي؟
My uncle.
عمويم
Oh, you do have family?
س خانواده هم داري؟
No.
نه
But you just said you had an uncle.
ولي الان فتي يه عمو داري
He's dead.
اون مرده
Oh...
...اوه
Is this good?
اين خوبه؟
That's wonderful.
شفت آوره
OK, ready? God!
!باشه،حاضري؟خدا جون
You're acting ridiculous. It's not so bad.
مضحک بازي ميکني.بدک نيست
That looks like it belongs there.
بنظر مياد مال همونجا باشه
Where is it?
اون کجاست؟
It's right there.
درست اونجا
Oh yes! It belongs there.
آره!مال همونجاست
Hi. Can I come in?
سلام.ميتونم بيام تو؟
OK.
باشه
Where'd you learn that?
اونو کجا ياد رفتي؟
Learn what?
ي رو ياد رفتم؟
The piece of music you just played?
اون قطعه موسيقي که اجرا کردي؟
It's what I hear in my head.
اونو توي سرم ميشنوم
Do it again.
دوباره اجراش کن
It's hard. Someone had to teach it to you.
سخته.يکي بايد اونو يادت داده باشه
You don't remember?
يادت نمياد؟
No.
نه
Maybe in your other life. The one you had before us.
شايد توي زندي ديرت.کسيکه قبل ازما باهاش بودي
I don't know.
نميدونم
Everything is new about you now.
حالا هريزي درباره تو جديده
Your clothes, your hair, your whole life.
لباسهات، موهات، کل زنديت
This is the last...
...اين آخريشه
I think it's time to put the last thing away. Don't you?
فکر کنم وقتشه آخري رو هم بندازي دور مه نه؟
Everything is new about you now.
حالا همه يزت جديده
Goodnight.
شب بخير
Oh yes.
اوه بله
My boy, we're going to have fun.
سرم،ما ميخوايم سررم باشيم
That's good, that's good.
خوبه،خوبه
Alrighty then.
س خيلي خوب
You know Victoria's big recital is next month, right?
ميدوني تک نوازي بزر ويکتوريا ماه ديه است، درسته؟
D'you remember me telling you about where I grew up? In New York City?
يادته که فتم کجا بزر شدم؟ توي نيويورک؟
Carnegie Hall!
!تالار کارني
Yeah, well, that's where Victoria and I are from. That's our home.
آره،خوبه، من و ويکتوريا مال همونجاييم.اون خونه ماست
This is your home.
اين خونه توئه
No, no, this is just a temporary home.
نه،نه، اين فقط يه خونه موقتيه
We only came here so Victoria could attend school.
مااينجا اومديم تا ويکتوريا مدرسه اش رو ادامه بده
What I'm trying to say, Danny, is...
...دني،ميخوام بم که
After Victoria graduates, we're gonna go back home.
بعد از فارغ التحصيلي ويکتوريا ميخوايم بررديم خونه
We're gonna go back to New York.
بايد بررديم نيويورک
And I don't know how this would work out but...
...منم نميدونم طور ميشه ولي
We would really like for you to come with us
ما خيلي دوست داريم که تو با ما بياي
because we've begun to think of you as family and,
آخه ما روي تو بعنوان فاميل فکر کرده بوديم
well, that's what families do.
خوب،اين کاريه که فاميلها ميکنن
They stick together.
اونها هميشه باهمديه هستن
Or at least this one does.
يا لااقل اين بارهستيم
So what do you say?
خوب ي ميي؟
2, 3, 4, 5... This is your pay.
ببين...2،3،4،5اين حسابته
Fifty-fifty. Partners. You and me.
نجاه-نجاه.ارتنرها.تو ومن
Happy?
خوشحالي؟
What do I do with it?
باهاش کار کنم؟
Anything you want.
هرکاري که ميخواي
Fuck's sake, man!
لعنتي،مرد
Danny!
!دني
Alright, Danny, look at you! You look great, man!
!هي...دني ، ببينمت!تو فوق العاده اي،مرد
Look at... You smell divine, pal, I tell ya!
شبيه آدم حسابي ها شدي ،رفيق
I don't know what you're wearing.
نميدونم داري ي ميوشي
Well, fancy bumping into you, eh.
عقلت تکون خورده ، هان
Boss sends me out. Get some mangos and papayas
رئيس منو ميفرسته بيرون که برم سراغ نخود سياه
and look what I find instead. A lemon. Whoa, whoa, whoa!
ببين به جاش ي يدا کردم.يه ليموترش
Your uncle Bart has been sick with worry, mate.
عمو بارت تو از نراني مريض شده ،رفيق
Yeah! His little pet all lost in the world.
آره!سولي کويکش ديه نيست
It's all he keeps on talking about, honestly.
اين همه اون يزيه که اون صادقانه درباره اش حرف ميزنه
"Where's my Little Danny?"
"دني کوولوي من کجاست؟"
He's dead.
اون مرده
Who told you that?
ه کسي به تو فت؟
I saw.
خودم ديدم
Well, you saw wrong, mate, because he's very, very much alive.
خوب،اشتباهي ديدي،رفيق.ون اون خيلي هم زنده هست
And very much looking forward to you coming home.
و خيلي هم دلش ميخواد که برردي خونه
Not my home anymore.
خونه من ديه نه
Not my home anymore. Why?
خونه من نه.را؟
You got a new home, have you, Danny? Eh?
يه خونه تازه رفتي؟دني؟
Oooh, hey! You got a new family as well?
يه خونواده تازه دست و ا کردي؟
I tell you what,
ببين بهت ي ميم
if you don't come home like a good little bitch,
اه مثل يه کوولوي خوب نياي خونه
Uncle Bart will send a few of the boys out to pay a visit to your new home?
اونوقت عمو بارت ند تا از سرا رو ميفرسته که يه ناهي به خونه تو بندازن
Would you like that? Wouldn't be too hard to find,
همين رو ميخواي؟ فهميدنش نبايد زياد سخت باشه
what with you shopping here and all.
اينکه با ه کسي مياي خريد
Look who's come home to his loving Uncle Bart!
ناه کن ه کسي به عشق عمو بارت خودش اومده خونه
Give me a hug.
بيا تو بغلم
How's my boy? You're looking smart.
سرم طوره؟بنظر مياد باهوشه
Oh, look at her! Ragner the prat!
!ناش کن
We've missed you around here, haven't we?
همين ورا مت کرده بوديم،نه؟
Yeah, we've definitely missed you, Danny.
.آره،حتماً مت کرده بوديم ،دني
Must've really scared you, that accident, all that shooting.
بايد خيلي ترسيده باشي اون حادثه، اونهمه تيراندازي
Yeah, me too.
آره، منم همينطور
Look at me.
منو ببين
I've been laid up for a month.
يه ماهه که ازکارو زندي افتادم
But I'm back.
ولي حالا برشتم
And I'm ready to roll.
و آماده کار هستم
You ready to roll?
تو آماده اي؟
I have a question.
يه سوال دارم
You? A question?
تو؟يه سوال؟
Wonders never cease. It's not about that bleedin' piano again, is it?
شفتيها تمومي نداره درباره اون يانوي خوني که نيست، هست؟
No.
نه
Listen, as I'm so pleased to have you home,
وش کن،ون خيلي خوشحالم که خونه اي
I'll answer one question. Go on, fire away.
به يه سوال جواب ميدم.زود باش
Did you know my mom?
مادرمو ميشناختي؟
Your mum?
مادرت؟
Why would I know your mum?
را بايد مادرتو بشناسم؟
I found you in the street.
من تو رو توي خيابون يدا کردم
Laying on the pavement.
کف خيابون دراز کشيده بودي
You was half dead, you couldn't even talk. You was just laying there.
نيمه جون بودي. حتي نميتونستي حرف بزني فقط دراز کشيده بودي
No one wanting you,
کسي منتظرت نبود
no one caring whether you lived or died.
کسي براش مهم نبود که زنده اي يا مرده
Except me.
بجز من
I've told you all this before, remember?
اينها رو قبلاً به تو فتم،يادته؟
All right, listen. I'll show you stuff that'll jog your memory.
باشه، وش کن، ميخوام يه يزي نشونت بدم که حافظه ات رو راه بندازه
That was our first collaboration, that was.
.اون اولين همکاري ما بود اولين همکاري بود
Danny, what's this sudden fascination with the past?
دني، ي شده که اين دفعه شيفته ذشته ات شدي؟
Have you been talking to people?
با مردم صحبت کردي؟
No.
نه
You want some good advice from your Uncle Bart, eh?
ميخواي يه نصيحت خوب از طرف عمو بارت خودت بشنوي؟
Don't dwell on the past.
توي ذشته نمون
Look to the future.
آينده رو ببين
The past is behind you. The future is ahead of you.
ذشته شت توئه و آينده يش روي تو
Like a bright glittering mountain of gold.
مثل کوه درخشاني از طلا که برق ميزنه
You wanna know what your future is, Danny?
واقعاً ميخواي از آينده خودت بدوني،دني؟
I'm thrilled you're here.
من از اينکه تو اينجايي هيجان زده ام
We've been waiting for you.
ما منتظرت بوديم
Has our friend been practicing on you?
دوستمون با تو تمرين ميکرده؟
Had an accident.
يه حادثه داشتم
Right this way.
از اين طرف
Show's about to start. How's our boy?
نمايش براي شروعه.حال سر ما طوره؟
He has never been better.
بهتره
I hope so. Because he certainly has his work cut out for him tonight.
اميدوارم باشه.ون اون امشب
I've dressed him in his Sunday best.
بهترين لباس يکشنبه رو وشوندمش
We are expecting more of a show this time.
ايندفعه بيشتر از يه نمايش انتظار داريم
Well, don't worry about it.
خوب،نرانش نباشيد
We've got it all worked out.
ما خيلي براش زحمت کشيديم
Haven't we Danny?
اينطور نيست  دني؟
Kill him! Kill him!
!بکشش!بکشش
Get him out!
بندازش بيرون
Listen! Give these toffs a bit of a show.
وش کن! يه کم از يه نمايش رو به اين آقايون نشون بده
Play him for a bit.
يه کم باهاش بازي کن
Make it look as if there might be a chance you could loose.
ولي کاري نکن که شانست رو از دست بدي
Gentlemen!
آقا
Got it?
آماده هست؟
To the death!
تا اي مر
Right, down you go!
خوب،برو ايين
What's wrong with you?
مشکلي برات يش اومده؟
I don't want to hurt people anymore.
نميخوام مردم بيشتر از اين صدمه ببينن
Excuse me?
بخشيد؟
Danny, that's what you do. You hurt people.
دني،اون کاريه که تو کردي تو به مردم آسيب رسوندي
Not anymore.
ديه نه
What the hell's happened to you?
ه بلايي سرت اومده؟
Who's been filling your head with this crap?
ه کسي سرت رو با اين رنديات ر کرده؟
Anything wrong, gentlemen?
مشکلي هست،آقا؟
No, no, no, we're fine. No, just... Just discussing strategy.
نه،نه،نه، ما خوبيم. نه فقط ...فقط سر روش کار بحث داريم
Of course.
البته
Listen to me, you little shit.
به من وش بده، کثافت کوولو
You're gonna get down there and you're gonna do your job
يا همين الان اونجا ياده ميشي و ميري کارتو انجام ميدي
or I'm gonna have your balls on a stick!
يا اينکه من با تخمهات هاکي بازي ميکنم
Now, go!
!حالا برو
I don't want to hurt people anymore.
نميخوام مردم بيشتر از اين آسيب ببينن
I'll make you a deal. If you go down there tonight and do your job,
يه قراري باهات ميذارم اه امشب بري اون ايين و کارتو بکني
I promise you, tomorrow,
به تو قول ميدم،فردا
I will buy you the nicest piano in the whole bleeding city.
بهترين يانوي شهر بليدين رو برات بخرم
How's that?
طوره؟
I don't want to hurt people anymore.
نميخوام مردم بيشتر از اين آسيب ببينن
Then you're dead.
س تو ديه مردي
Go get him Tiger!
تاير ببرش
Come on! Come on! Danny, come on!
!يالا!بجنب!دني،يالا
What's going on?
حالا ي ميشه؟
Well, you said you wanted it to be more of an entertainment.
خوب، تو فتي که ميخواستم بيشتر از يه سررمي باشه
But he's not even fighting back.
اما
Pick it up!
اونو بردار
Use it! Danny!
!ازش استفاده کن!دني
Danny!
!دني
I think we have a problem here.
فکر ميکنم اينجا يه مشکل داريم
What?
ي؟
These people came to see a fight, not a bloody game of tag.
اين مردم اينجا اومدن که يه دعوا تماشا کنن نه يه رم به هواي خوني
Do you mind if I get a little creative with the format?
فکر ميکني
It's your show.
اين نمايش توئه
Danny, you're ruining me here!
دني،تو داري اينجا نابودم ميکني
It's time to make some money.
وقتشه يه کم ول در بياريم
Danny, you're gonna get killed!
دني ، اينجوري کشته ميشي
Fight back!
بررد بجن
Danny!
دني
Weapons!!
سلاح ها
Kill him!
بکشش
If you don't kill him, I don't get paid.
اه اونو نکشي،ولي به من نميرسه
Kill him, for Christ's sake!
بکشش،بخاطر مسيح
Come on!
!بجنب
Or they'll kill me! Kill him!
!والا اونها منو ميکشن!اونو بکش
Fuck it!
لعنتي اونو بکش
No more killing!
!ديه کشتن بسه
I decide when there's no more killing! I! Me!
!من تصميم مييرم کي کشتن بسه!من!من
The master commands and the dog obeys!
وقتي صاحب دستور ميده،س اطاعت ميکنه
I will kill you!
!تو رو ميکشم
Put him to bed.
بندازينش توي جاش
Why'd he leave?
را رفت؟
Maybe he had some things to do.
شايد کاري داشت که انجامش بده
But I thought he was happy here.
ولي من فکر ميکردم که اون اينجا خوشحاله
Well, sweetie, sometimes being happy just isn't enough.
خوب،عزيزم،بعضي وقتها فقط خوشحال بودن کافي نيست
Sometimes people have to go back and fix the things
اهي اوقات افراد  مجبورن قبل از خوشحال بودن برردن و مسائلي رو برطرف کنن
that made them unhappy before they were happy.
که باعث ناراحتي اونها شده
But I could help him.
ولي من ميتونستم کمکش کنم
I know.
ميدونم
Sometimes people have to do things themselves.
اهي مردم بايد خودشون بعضي کارها رو انجام بدن
You lied to me!
تو به من دروغ فتي
Ow, you bastard!
!حرامزاده
What are you doing in my fucking chair, you little retard?
تو روي صندلي لعنتي من کار ميکني عقب افتاده کوولو؟
You lied to me!
تو به من دروغ فتي
This is my mother. You knew my mother!
!اين مادر منه. تو مادرمو ميشناختي
She was a whore.
اون يه فاحشه بود
Do you know what a whore is, Danny?
ميدوني يه فاحشه ه آدميه،دني؟
Money for sex.
ول براي سکس کردن
Like the girls I bring here.
مثل دخترهايي که ميارم اينجا
I did everything I could to help her...
...من همه کار کردم،ميتونستم کمکش کنم
I liked your mum. She understood me.
من مادرتو دوست داشتم.اون منو مي فهميد
If there'd ever been anybody really special, it would have been her.
اه يه آدم استثنايي هم وجود داشت،اون آدم مادرت بود
When she died, I felt I owed it to her to raise you.
وقتيکه مرد، احساس کردم توي بزر کردن تو، مديونشم
To protect you.
توي مراقبت از تو
Look, her picture's here.
ببين،عکسش اينجاست
Look...
...ناه کن
I'm sorry if I lied to you, Danny.
متاسفم که به تو دروغ فتم،دني
It was out of love.
بخاطر عشق بود
Now, let's go and make up some of that money
حالا،بيا بريم و يه کم از اون ول رو برردونيم
you lost for me the other night. Right?
يه شب ديه بخاطر من ضرر کردي.درسته؟
You know, Danny,
ميدوني،دني
sometimes
بعضي وقتها
in families you need a little tragedy just to bring everybody back together.
توي خانواده ها يه تراژدي کويک لازمه تا دوباره همه دور هم جمع بشن
Absolutely, boss. Y'know, it's like me and me brother in Blackpool.
حق با توئه، رئيس درست مثل من و برادرم توي بلاکول
We used to go down the beach every...
...از جزر دريا استفاده ميکرديم هر
Excuse me! Like where's the manners? I'm talking!
!ميبخشيد!ادبت کجاست؟دارم حرف ميزنم
I was just validating, boss!
!فقط داشتم تاييد ميکردم،رئيس
Did I ask for a validation?
من از تو تاييد خواستم ؟
No but I thought, y'know...
...نه ولي فکر کردم،ميدوني
Will you shut your yap?
ميشه ديه زوزه نکني؟
Now, I've lost the train of me thought. What was I saying?
حالا،رشته افکارم اره شد.داشتم ي ميفتم؟
Families.
خانواده ها
Right. Right, yeah.
درسته.درسته،آره
How they should be together.
اينکه طور بايد باهم باشن
Exactly.
دقيقاً
Families should be together.
خانواده ها بايد باهم باشن
No matter what.
اهميت ندارده ي ميشه
Danny! What the fuck are you doing?
دني!ه غلطي ميکني؟
Slow down bastard
آروم حرومزاده
Get off. Jesus, boss!
!ولش کن.يا مسيح،رئيس
My mother. She was a whore.
مادرم.اون يه فاحشه بود
Look... Not that I'm an expert, but I have to say, she does not look like,
ببين...نه اينکه يه کارشناس باشم ولي بايد بم، اون شبيه
y'know, that kind of woman.
ميدوني، شبيه اونجور زنها نيست
What does that mean?
منظورت يه؟
Well, she's playing the piano.
خوب،اون داره يانو ميزنه
What else is in the photo?
توي عکس ديه ي هست؟
There's a bunch of students in uniform.
يه روه  دانشجو با لباس فرم هست
There's a big stained glass window.
يه نجره شيشه اي نقشداربزر هست
It looks like an academy or something...
...بنظر يه دانشاه يا يزي مياد
And there's two baby grands back to back.
و يه به و يه خانوم ، کنار هم شت يانو هستن
What kind of baby grands?
کدومشون  يانو ميزنن؟
Pleyel, both.
فکر کنم ، هردوشون
I've got an idea.
من يه فکري کردم
Excellent job you made of tuning the pianos in the concert hall, young man.
توي کوک کردن يانوهاي سالن کنسرت کارت فوق العاده بود، مرد جوان
Why, thank you ma'am. Thank you.
را،ممنون مامان.ممنون
Last fellow we had in was so drunk he never found the hall.
آخرين کسيکه اينجا داشتيم اونقدر مست بود که نتونست تالار رو يدا کنه
Ended up tuning the plumbing.
آخرش هم داشت لوله ها رو کوک ميکرد
Terrible mess.
افتضاح بود
Danny?
دني؟
Thirty two years of faces and I've never forgotten one.
حتي بعد از 32 سال هم هره کسي رو فراموش نکردم
Especially this one.
مخصوصاً اين يکي
Why especially this one?
را مخصوصاً اين يکي رو؟
Brilliant girl. Absolutely brilliant.
اين دختر جواهره.واقعاً جواهره
Destined for great things we were sure of it.
براي يزهاي زيادي عازم شد،مابه اون اعتماد داشتيم
And then one day she just disappeared.
و بعد يه روز ناديد شد
We thought she'd gone home. We thought maybe it was financial.
فکر کرديم رفته خونه.فکر کرديم شايد بخاطر ول بوده
We knew she had some money problems.
ميدونستيم از نظر ولي يه کم مشکل داره
But then her family from China wrote to ask
ولي بعد خونواده اش از ين نوشتن که
why she hadn't got in touch with them. Had a little boy and everything.
را اون باهاشون تماس نرفته اون به کوولو همه يزشون بود
Very strange... Sad...
...خيلي غريب...غمين
Ah ha! Here she is.
اون اينجاست
You OK?
تو خوبي؟
I'm OK.
خوبم
You're sure?
مطمئني؟
Sure.
مطمئن
Hello!
سلام
Guys?
به ها؟
Sam?
سم؟
Danny?
دني؟
You were supposed to pick me up.
ميخواين غافليرم کنين
I'm sorry.
متاسفم
You got another picture?
عکس ديه اي نرفتيد؟
The lady said she was an excellent piano player.
اون خانم فت که اون يه يانيست فوق العاده بود
I'm sure.
مطئنم
You want to hear what she played?
ميخواي بشنوي اون ي اجرا ميکرد؟
How?
طوري؟
See? Mozart sonata number eleven.
ميبيني؟سوناتاي موزارت شماره يازده
Your mom didn't just play music. She played beautiful music.
مادرت موسيقي رو فقط اجرا نميکرد اون موسيقي رو قشن اجرا ميکرد
Magical music. Great music.
موسيقي سحرآميز.موزيک فوق العاده
I'm sorry to inconvenience you,
متاسفم که ناراحتت کردم
but I really do need to know where to find him.
ولي من واقعاً ميخوام بدونم کجا ميتونم يداش کنم
No, I never seen him before in my life.
نه،تاحالا توي عمرم نديدمش
Let me rephrase the question.
بزار سئوال رو اصلاح کنم
What is this?
اين يه؟
Oh Sam, oh Sam, he remembered.
اوه سم،اوه سم،اون يادش اومد
I was playing the piano, the music and he remembered...
...داشتيم يانو ميزديم و اون يادش اومد
Slow down. Slow down. Remembered what?
آروم باش،آروم باش.ي رو يادش اومد؟
His mother. Who killed his mother.
مادرش.کسي رو که مادرشو کشت
You remember who killed your mother?
يادته کي مادرتو کشت؟
Sam, we have to go!
سم،بايد بريم
Wait, son, wait now. Before we go running off anywhere,
صبر کن،سر،فعلا بمون.قبل از اينکه از کوره در بريم
let's stop and take a deep breath and decide what's going on.
بزار بمونيم و يه نفس عميق بکشيم و ببينيم ي يش مياد
Tell me from the top. Danny?
از بالا برام بو.دني؟
Danny, wait... Listen to me.
دني،صبر کن...به من وش بده
Danny, wait!
دني،وايستا
Will you just listen?
تو فقط وش کن؟
No time.
وقت نيست
Danny, Danny, wait!
دني،دني،صبر کن
Boss, these boys aren't up to it. He's fucked off.
رئيس،اين سرها در حد اون نيستن.اون در رفته
Get in there. Oi!
شما هم برين !اوي
I want him alive! He's not worth shit to me dead!
زنده ميخوامش!مرده اش ، يه آشغال هم نمي ارزه
Go on!
!برو
Shit!
!آشغال
You'd better get in there.
شما بهتره بريد اون تو
You! You! That way!
!تو!تو!از اون طرف
That's it.
اونه
That son of a bitch!
اون درس
It's all going on the bill, Danny boy!
!همه يز با ول يش ميره،دني
You hear me?
وشت با منه؟
It's going on the bill. And you're gonna pay.
اسکناس همه يز رو يش ميبره.وتو ميخواي که ول بدي
You'll pay me back.
تو ولو به من برميردوني
Believe me, you're gonna pay! Bastard!
!باور کن، ولو ميدي!حرومزاده
You know, it was your fault really.
ميدوني،همه اش تقصير تو بود
You were such a scrapper. I could see the potential.
تو اينقدر دعوايي بودي.تونستم استعدادتو ببينم
With the right training, my own little guided missile.
با آموزش صحيح،موشک هدايت شونده کوولوي من
Listen Danny, I know we've had some rough patches
وش کن دني،ميدونم يه کم وصله هاي ناجور به هم زديم
but what family doesn't, eh?
ولي کدوم خانواده اي هست که اينطوري نباشه،هان؟
Listen, you get over this business.
وش کن،تو کار اين کاسبي رو ساختي
We can have plenty more.
ما ميتونيم خيلي بيشتر داشته باشيم
Shit!
!آشغال
Find him!
!يداش کنين
C'mon! Hello-o!
!يالا!سلـــام
How did he get in there?
طور رفته اون تو؟
He's in there!
اون اونجاست
Shut up. Let me listen.
خفه شو.بزار وش کنم
Stop breathing down my fucking ear!
!زير وش لعنتي من نفس نکش
Sorry, boss.
ببخشيد،رئيس
Move back.
برو عقب
Clever little bastard.
حرومزاده کوولوي زرن
Wait here.
همينجا صبر کنين
All of you, just wait here.
همه تون،اينجا منتظر مي مونين
Danny!
!دني
Where are you?
کجايي؟
Bastards!
حرومزاده
Pajamas?
لباس خواب ؟
Fucking pajamas!
لباس خواب لعنتي
You ungrateful little bastard!
تو خيلي نمک بحرامي
Where are you?
کجايي؟
This is it?
همينه؟
This is your refuge?
اينجا مخفياهته؟
Your home away from home?
خيلي از خونه دور هست؟
This is your place of... awakening?
اينجا جاي ... بيدار شدنته؟
Art,
هنر
books,
کتابها
music?
موسيقي؟
For what?
براي ي؟
Did it make you a better person?
اون تو رو آدم بهتري کرده؟
Look what you made of it.
ببين از تو ي ساخته
Nice people took you in.
آدمهاي خوب تو رو درک کردن
They give you everything.
اونها همه يزبه تو دادن
And look how you repay them.
و ببين تو طوري جوابشونو ميدي
You destroyed their lives.
تو زنديشونو نابود کردي
Like you'll destroy any life.
دلت ميخواد همه زندي ها رو از بين ببري
That's because you're not meant for this kind of life, Danny.
ون تو با اين نوع زندي ميونه اي نداري،دني
You're a dog.
تو يه سي
You're my dog.
تو س مني
I fed you. I trained you. I own you.
من به تو غذا دادم.آموزش دادم.من صاحبتم
And I should kill you. Like any responsible owner would do to a dog
و مجبورم بکشمت، مثل هر صاحب مسئوليت ذيري بايد کاري براي سي بکنم
that caused this much pain, this much suffering.
که باعث اين همه مصيبته اين همه درد و رنجه
But...
...اما
The heart...
...دل
Come home, Danny.
بيا خونه ،دني
All's forgiven.
همه يز قابل بخششه
You'll be safe.
تو در امان هستي
You'll be back in a world that you understand.
برميردي به دنيايي که مي فهميش
The only world you'll ever understand.
تنها دنيايي که تاحالا فهميدي
What do you say?
ي ميي؟
Forgive and forget?
ميبخشي و فراموش ميکني
I know just how confusing the world can get.
ميدونم دنيا قدر يج کننده هست
We'll make it simple again.
ما اونو ساده مي کنيم
You, me...
...تو و من
Our cozy little life.
زندي کويک و رم و نرممون رو
Come on, Danny,
يالا ، دني
come on.
يالا
Come on. Yes, this is my boy.
بجنب.آره،اين سر منه
Yes, come on, come on...
آره،يالا،يالا
Welcome home Danny...
...به خونه خوش اومدي دني
I am home.
من توي خونه ام
No, Danny!
!نه،دني
Don't! He's gonna kill him!
!نه!ميخواد اونو بکشه
Don't do this Danny! Don't.
!اينکارو نکن،دني
He killed my mother.
اون مادرمو کشت
This won't bring her back! And you'll be just like him!
اين کار اونو برنميردونه و تو هم ميشي درست مثل اون
He is me. We're both animals.
اون مال منه.هردوي ما حيوونيم
Fucking dog!
س لعنتي
No, you're not an animal! If you kill him,
نه،تو حيوون نيستي!اه اونو بکشي
Danny, everything you've done to make yourself happy will be lost.
دني، هرکاري رو که براي خوشحال کردن خودت کردي از بين ميبري
Don't listen to this crap!
به اين مزخرفات وش نکن
They'll lock you in a cage forever!
اونها تو رو براي هميشه توي يه قفس زنداني ميکنن
We are animals!
ما حيوونيم
No Danny. No.
نه دني.نه
You know why he wants you to kill him? It's the only way he can justify what...
ميدوني را ميخواد که بکشيش؟ اين تنها راهيه که ميتونه به خودش حق بده
Danny, listen to me.
دني،به من وش کن
Remember your mother.
مادرتو به ياد بيار
Remember what I did to her. I screwed her every day.
يادته باهاش يکار کردم .هر روز اونو مست ميکردم
I mounted her like the bitch she was!
بعد ون يه فاحشه بود،ميريدم روش
You'll never be anything but a dog.
تو هميشه يه س هستي
You'll never escape what you are.
هيوقت نميتوني از اوني که هستي فرار کني
You'll never escape what I made you.
هيوقت نميتوني از يزي که از تو ساختم خلاص بشي
A killer.
يه قاتل
That's what you are.
اين همونيه که تو هستي
That's what you'll always be.
همون يزيکه هميشه خواهي بود
Now, be a good dog.
حالا، يه س خوب باش
Kill me, get it over with! Come on! Kill me!
!منو بکش، کارتو تموم کن! يالا! منو بکش
Shut the hell up!
خفه شو
That man could talk some serious shit.
اون مرد داشت زيادي رت و رت ميفت
You're alright with that thing around your neck?
با اون يزيکه دور ردنته راحتي؟
Is it OK?
خوب هست؟
I'd say it was a decided improvement.
فته بودم تصميم خوبيه
Ladies and gentlemen the recipient of the 2 hundred and,
خانومها و آقايون، دارنده دو هزار امتياز
college excellent in piano, Miss Victoria Mills!
دانشجوي ممتاز دانشکده،خانم ويکتوريا ميلز
My selection tonight is dedicated to someone wonderful.
انتخاب امشب من اختصاص داره به يه نفر
That's you.
اون تويي
Oh no, no, it's not me she's talking about.
نه،نه،اون درباره من حرف نميزنه
Someone whose life was, quite literally, saved by music.
کسيکه تمام زنديش،با موسيقي نجات يدا کرده
That's you my boy.
.سرم ،اون تويي